const quizData = [
  {
    question: "What is a gradient in CSS?",
    option1: "A color that remains the same throughout",
    option2: "A gradual transition between two or more colors",
    option3: "A background image",
    option4: "a yellowish green color",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of gradient flows in a straight line?",
    option1: "Radial gradient",
    option2: "linear gradient",
    option3: "conic gradient",
    option4: "angular gradient",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the default direction of a linear gradient?",
    option1: "Top to bottom",
    option2: "Left to right",
    option3: "Bottom to top",
    option4: "right to left",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many colors are required for a gradient to work?",
    option1: "One",
    option2: "Minimum of Two",
    option3: "At least three",
    option4: "none",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of start and stop points in gradients?",
    option1: "To specify the direction of the gradient",
    option2: "To specify the color of the gradient",
    option3: "To specify the angle of the gradient",
    option4: "To specify where the color should start and stop blending",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of gradient radiates from a central point?",
    option1: "Linear gradient",
    option2: "Radial gradient",
    option3: "Conic gradient",
    option4: "Spiral gradient",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "How can you specify the center point of a radial gradient?",
    option1: "Using the at keyword",
    option2: "Using the from keyword",
    option3: "Using the to keyword",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which type of gradient rotates around a central point?",
    option1: "Linear gradient",
    option2: "Radial gradient",
    option3: "Conic gradient",
    option4: "Spiral gradient",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "How can you specify the starting point of a conic gradient?",
    option1: "Using the from keyword",
    option2: "Using the to keyword",
    option3: "Using the at keyword",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Can you use multiple gradients in a single background property?",
    option1: "No",
    option2: "Yes, separated by commas",
    option3: "Yes, separated by semicolons",
    option4: "yes, separated by plus sign",
    ans: 2,
  },
];

export default quizData;
